





Summary

Jump to Section

Aperformance-driven Software Engineer - cum - Solution Manager with 3.5+ years of experience in targeting assignments based on Java, ReactJs & MySQL. Leading a team of developers and ensuring a planned sprint execution and quality code delivery on time with a focus on training, shaping and leading bright young minds into the UI landscape.

Work Experience

HighRadius Technologies Pvt. Ltd. as Solution Manager -Java Jul 2017 to Till Date

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills |

• HighRadius Technologies Pvt. Ltd. as Solution Manager -Java Jul 2017 to Jul 2017

Manage, mentor and develop a team of 15+ developers in ensuring 100% TQVS Score (Time Quality Value Satisfaction) for Autonomous Collections & Freeda Team.

Analyze requirements, prepare the technical design and oversee development and testing process for achieving the release milestones by defining the scope of development.

Interview new talents applying for a job as a Full-Stack Developer at the mid-entry level for the current office location. Knowledge of using framework and tools to provide insights while delegating resources to develop features using ReactJs, Java and MySQL.

JULY 2017 - JUNE 2019 HighRadius Technologies Pvt. Ltd. | Hyderabad, Telangana Software Engineer JULY 2017 - JUNE 2019 HighRadius Technologies Pvt. Ltd. | Hyderabad, Telangana Software Engineer

^ Back to Top

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Computer Science and Engineering) from KALINGA INSTITUTE OF INDUSTRIAL TECHNOLOGY (KIIT), BHUBANESWAR in 2017

PG: in 0

1

Important

 Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld

IT Skills

| Skill Name | Version Last Used Experience |
|-----------------|------------------------------|
| CORE JAVA, J2EE | |
| EXTJS | |
| MySQL | |
| Reactjs | |

^ Back to Top

Languages Known

| Language | Proficiency | Read | Write | Speak |
|----------|-------------|------|-------|-------|
| English | | | | |
| Hindi | | | | |
| Odia | | | | |

^ Back to Top

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Physically Challenged: No

Job Type: Permanent Employment Status: Full time

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.